You're just having a bad dream.
That's all, baby.
That's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've
seen things that you haven't.
You know what I do
when I have a bad dream?
I close my eyes and I
think of something nice.
Like being here with you.
Hurry up, sweetheart.
We're gonna be late.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see someone
ring my doorbell?
No.
Okay, thanks.
I cleaned everything
away, sweetheart.
Everything is exactly
the way it was before.
They're clean and shiny.
Look. Look. You see?
Okay, all right.
Just close your eyes.
Well, hello, sailor.
Hi!
Permission to come aboard?
Honey, hold this.
So sorry we couldn't make it yesterday.
Somebody was working late again.
How're you doing, Sal?
I'm good. How are you?
I'm all right.
Look at you.
Do you like it?
You look great.
Really? I just
kinda threw it on.
She's had outfits
laid out for a week.
You're such a liar.
You know my husband.
I don't listen to what he says.
You know that.
I brought my really good friend, Heather.
She's so nice.
Promise me you'll be attentive.
How're you doing, man?
She's not to bring anyone.
You don't like her? Believe me, she's
the best looking of Sally's friends.
Which it doesn't say much.
I asked you not to.
You're living on a boat with an 18-year
old boy and you're saying no girls.
Greg, this is Heather.
She's a very good friend of mine, and
I just thought you guys should meet.
Hi.
Can you just excuse me
for a moment?
Jess. You okay?
I don't think so.
Hey. What happened?
Hey. What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing
to apologize for.
What is it? Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Well, listen, we don't have to
go today if you don't want to.
No, we do. I-I wanna go.
You sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay, come on.
Come up here.
This is Sally and
her husband, Downey.
This is Heather, Sally's friend.
You remember Victor.
So let's go sailing!
Okay.
Hey.
You okay?
Is Greg okay?
He's fine. He's upstairs.
You've been asleep
for a couple of hours.
I had this terrible dream.
What about?
I don't remember.
I wouldn't worry.
Apparently bad dreams cure
you of real life stress.
As indeed does champagne.
You want some?
Yeah.
Downey, wanna give me
a hand, please?
Actually, Victor, I'm a guest of the
Captain's, but yes, I will help you.
Victor, what was that
back there at the harbor?
What?
I asked Jess if she was all
right and you said no.
You told me she was bringing
the little boy along.
When I was walking with her in
the harbor I asked where he was.
She couldn't remember.
She stared into space
for like 20 seconds
and then she said
he's at school.
So?
Well, it's Saturday.
Ain't no school today.
Her son goes to a special needs
school and it's open every day.
Be nice to her.
All right.
Do you boys sunbathe together?
Sometimes.
The champagne is not great
but it is cold. Want some?
No thanks.
Okay, more for me.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm sorry, I didn't
realize how tired I was.
You apologize one more time, and
I'm gonna throw you overboard.
Here.
You all right?
Yeah.
He thinks we're a fishing boat.
He's gonna go hungry.
You want to steer?
Nah.
Go on.
Which way do I aim?
You're gonna aim that way.
It's easy, right?
So, she's a waitress
at some diner.
At least there they talk.
They became friends.
Oh, and she has
an autistic son.
So they're just friends.
Sally!
What do you want me to say? I'm
sorry she has a retarded son?
Yeah!
Well, I'm sorry. You know, that's
not Greg's problem, that's hers.
What is it, is it the shorts?
No! Heather, Greg's been my
friend for a really long time.
I can't just sit back and
watch him get shaken down.
She isn't doing that.
Well, I hope not because
Greg is far too trusting.
I'm kinda linking the boy.
Uh, no, you're not. Can you please
go up there and talk to Greg?
I really think the two of you
will be perfect for each other.
And I really don't like
seeing him with her.
Jess, are you ready?
Yeah, let her go.
Yeah.
Woo!
So, how do
you know everyone?
Victor, he's staying
with me for good.
He got in trouble at home.
He had to get away.
I found him sleeping behind
the store at the harbor.
You know, we got talking,
and now he lives here.
Just like that
you let him move in?
Well, I got three rooms.
I can't sleep in them all.
And Downey, I've known
him since I was a kid.
Sally, his wife, I know
her from high school.
I dated her for like four
days in the eighth grade,
so technically she's my ex.
They seem really nice.
Yeah. Except for the fact that
every year they feel obliged
to bring me an eligible girl.
Maybe they think you're lonely.
Do I give off lonely to you?
Sometimes.
When I come to see you at the
diner, I'm not lonely, I'm hungry.
Obviously yesterday
was different.
What happened yesterday?
Yesterday I was not hungry.
I came in with the sole purpose
of inviting you sailing.
You did?
I did.
Turn at port side.
We're losing wind.
Let me check it for just a sec.
So, things are okay with Tommy?
The same.
Every day is the same.
Tommy likes the things
to be a certain way. Yeah.
If I do one thing
differently, I lose him.
What's the matter? I've never
seen you like this before.
I don't know. I just, uh, I just
feel guilty when I'm not with Tommy.
That's because
you're a good mother.
But you can't be everywhere
all of the times.
Hey, guys. Oh!
How is it going?
We're good.
I was just wondering if I could
steal Jess away from you.
Sally's dying to talk to her.
We're kind of in the middle
of something right now.
No, no, it's okay.
I-I should circulate.
Hey, just for the record,
I'm not interested.
Yo, what the fuck?
Wind's dropped down on us.
It's not dropped, it's gone.
This is crazy.
You ever seen this before?
Yeah, yeah. Just not
quite so sudden.
Are we okay to get
home? There is no wind.
Yeah, yeah. We got an engine.
It's not a problem.
It's just, it's weird.
Greg?
Is that normal?
Okay, I'm fucking
freaked, what the fuck.
Triangle to coast guard. Over.
Coast guard, go ahead. Over.
We've just gone from seven knots to absolute zero.
You've got anything unusual? Over?
Nothing showing up. Over.
It's darkening up pretty quick out here.
Looks like an electrical storm. Over.
Help me.
Please. Can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
Killing everyone. They're
dead. They're all dead.
We hear you. What's your position?
Over.
Distressed caller, we hear you.
What are your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call?
We're not getting it anymore. Over.
Distressed caller, make another transmission.
What is your position?
Greg?
Get below deck now.
Get the life jackets.
Cut it. Cut the sail.
Vic, get the main sail down.
Get it down.
Vic!
No!
Get back.
Jess, take my hand.
Grab on.
Heather!
Vic!
Jess.
Are you okay?
All right.
Downey?
Are you guys okay?
Have you seen Heather? She
got lost through the window.
No. Come on, come on.
Heather!
Greg! Help me!
Sally. Sally.
Just give me your hand.
Heather!
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Tommy's at school, yeah?
He'll be looked after until we get back.
He'll be all right.
Thank God. Yo! Help us!
Help us. Help.
Help us. Over here.
Oh, God.
Hey. Hey.
Wait.
Come on, over here!
There, there. Over there.
I can see someone.
Yo, we need
some help down here.
Help us, please!
Hello. We need
some help down here.
Yeah, he's seen us.
He's seen us.
Oh, thank God.
Jump, jump, jump.
Okay. Jess, come on, come on.
Jess. Come on.
Come on, come on,
take my hand. Okay.
Okay. You okay?
You okay? Yeah?
Hey.
How is it?
See? I told you.
Hello?
Hello!
Do we wait?
No, let's go to the bridge.
We'll get the captain to put a
call out to the coast guard.
We'll get a search for Heather.
Come on.
Do you think Heather
would've made it on board?
Honey.
There's a chance, isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah,
there's a chance.
Hello?
Hello!
Somebody please help us?
Hello?
Where the
fuck is everybody?
You don't even
now where we're going.
Well, we're just, just
walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look
pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Come check this out.
This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
Jess.
Come on. Come on.
1932. It's the same.
Here's where we boarded.
Oh, yeah.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek god of the
winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods to the
task of pushing a rock up a mountain
and let it see
roll back down again.
That's a shitty punishment.
What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a
promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied it but I can't remember.
Can we just keep on moving, please?
Hello?
Whoever it was might wanna
come back for these.
Let me see?
These are mine.
These are my keys.
What are you talking about?
They're mine.
Bullshit.
This is, this is my house key.
This is my, my car key.
This is my son. See?
Wait. So you had them
with you on the yacht?
Yes.
It's gotta be Heather.
Come on.
How else did they get here?
It was Heather dropping her keys but not
bothering to say, "I didn't drown."
Why not?
Come on.
Heather?
Looks like you get your welcome
party, just not the welcome.
Heather!
Yo, Greg, what time you got?
Eleven thirty.
Heather.
Heather!
Where is everyone?
Sally! Please. Please.
I don't know where everyone is
but the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think
that it is but it's not,
so let's just go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we'll go home.
I saw someone.
Fuck.
Wait.
Hello?
Did you see who it was?
Was it Heather?
I didn't see.
I'm sorry.
Where're you going?
Why don't you
just help me out here?
What?
Just wait for Vic.
It's fine.
Why can't we go with him?
Let's just do as Greg says and
wait here for Victor, okay?
Fine.
I think Victor's in danger.
I'm not worried about Victor.
I'm sorry I'm acting weird.
It's just I'm having déjà vu
every time I turn a corner.
No, no. No.
I know this place.
No, you don't know this place.
You're just in shock.
That's funny.
What is it? What is it?
Is it Tommy?
Is it guilt? Is that what it is?
Do you feel guilty?
Hello?
Hello.
We're on the third floor. The bridge
is exactly two floors above us.
Greg, that was blood. Are
you just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored. They're
just letting off some steam.
What? They rescue us from the sea
and then they just hide for fun?
Yeah.
Well, what's your theory?
I don't know, but I'm not,
but I'm not in shock.
I'll be in the ball room.
I'm getting off this ship.
Jess, fuck! Don't you see that
this is all just in your mind?
Jess! Ships don't just magically
appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean, in
your world right now they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Jess. Jess, I'm sorry.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on, we're supposed
to meet them in the theater.
Heather!
Oh, my God. Shit.
Sally. Sal, come on.
Let's just go to the theater.
Downey, I can't see anymore blood.
I don't think she's in here.
To be honest with you, I don't
think she's even on the ship.
Okay. So whose blood was that?
Hello?
Downey? Sally?
Victor. What happened?
Oh, my God.
Stay with me, Greg.
Stay with me, man.
No. No!
You fucking bitch!
You shot him!
What?
He said you shot him.
I didn't!
Fucking liar!
I wasn't even with Greg!
He's dead! He's dead! Look!
God, you're a bitch!
Get your hands off him!
I didn't do it!
I was with Victor.
Someone attacked him.
Someone?
You think I did it?
Why did you tell us
to come to the theater?
I didn't. I... Sally, I didn't.
I didn't.
My God, you're
a fucking skitso.
Sally, no.
Sally!
No!
Downey!
Let it go. Let it go.
No!
Don't shoot. Please.
Please, don't shoot. Please.
I have a son. I have a son.
Shit.
Who are you? Tell me!
Who are you?
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way to get home.
What?
You have to kill them.
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
Over here. Come on. Hey!
Help us, please!
Help!
Hey. Hey.
Help us!
Please!
There, there. Over there.
I can see somebody.
Please!
Hello?
Looks like they decided
to scratch the welcome.
Let's go to the bridge.
We'll get the captain to put a
call out to the coast guard.
Hello!
Hello?
Where the
fuck is everybody?
Do you even
know where we're going?
Well, we're just, just
walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look
pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Jess, come on.
This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
Yeah. 1932.
It is the same.
Here's where we boarded.
Yeah. Aeolus.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek god of the
winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the gods to the
task of pushing a rock up a mountain
only to have it
roll back down again.
That's a shitty punishment.
What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a
promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied him and I can't remember.
Can we just keep on moving?
Hello?
Heather?
Hello!
Heather!
Sally. Please. I don't
know where everyone is.
But the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think
that it is but it's not,
so let's just go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we go home.
I saw someone.
Hello?
Hello.
Shit. How did you
get here so fast?
Victor, you got, you gotta listen to me.
We don't have much time.
Oh, what's going on?
Where's Greg?
He's dead.
What?
No, I mean, he was dead.
He's not dead now.
What are you saying?
Downstairs right now
is a copy of myself.
Me, walking and
talking with Greg.
Right.
There.
There's birds.
No, that was Downey's body.
I just left Downey back there.
How did you get here so fast?
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
No. Downey was there.
It was Downey's body.
There are bodies
all over this ship.
Your body is on the floor at the
restaurant with a hole in your head.
Listen, I'm gonna do
you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell
anyone about this.
It's the truth. Victor, we gotta
get off this ship right now.
You're saying there's
two of you now.
Yes.
And I'm dead in the restaurant.
You were killed.
Okay. So, I'm dead. Downey's in the water.
He's dead, too.
Is Sally okay?
See where I'm going
with this, right?
If we are dead and
there's two of you,
how are we all gonna
get off this ship?
We should never have
boarded this ship.
I knew something was wrong.
I should've forced you to stay on
the yacht and you'd all be alive.
I've gotta tell you I feel
pretty alive right now.
Soon you're gonna be dead. Everything
that happened to you, happened before.
I can't even believe
I'm talking this shit.
You will die and then, then
Downey and Sally and then Greg.
I didn't do this.
I didn't do it.
We're on the third level.
Greg, that was blood.
You just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
They see us, they get bored. They're
just letting off some steam.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just magically
appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean, in
your world right now they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Who are you?
Listen, listen to me.
Please, you have to listen.
Kill them all.
If they board, kill them.
Jess. Jess, you
gotta kill them.
Please, you have to listen.
Don't let them board.
No, no. No. Please, please.
Stop, stop them.
If they board, kill them.
Jess. Jess, you
gotta kill them.
If they board, kill them.
No, no. No. Please, please, stop.
Please, please stop.
Jess, Jess, Jess.
Fuck you!
Shit.
Tommy.
Is that blood?
Babe, come on. We're supposed
to meet them at the theater.
Victor.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
You know I didn't mean
to hurt you, right?
Now, I'm gonna try and get
us off this ship, okay?
Sally.
Sally?
Victor?
What happened?
You're not me.
You see? I'm not crazy.
Victor.
This didn't happen
before. Don't you see?
You tried to
strangle me, remember?
Now, you gotta be strong.
I'm gonna get the others.
Downey, do something.
Stay with me, man.
Do something.
I don't know what to do.
Is he dead? Is he dead?
Greg. Greg.
You fucking...
Listen, I'm not gonna hurt you.
We don't have much time.
Don't you point that thing.
Move!
Go, go, go.
I hit her. I think I hit her.
What's going on? Who was that?
It's starting over again.
That's what's going on.
Let's go.
We can't leave without Greg.
We'll come back for Greg. I promise.
Let's go, come on!
We can change the pattern.
Don't you see?
We change the pattern, we're not trapped.
Then we get off this thing.
She's fucking mad.
You think?
You have to listen to me.
No, I don't have
to listen to you.
Was it me that shot you?
I don't know.
Whoa, wait. Could we just
take a breath for a second?
Okay, Jess, I am prepared
to listen to you
and even to believe you, but
you gotta make some sense.
I'm making perfect sense. I'm gonna get
Victor, then we get off this ship.
Wait here.
And don't trust anyone.
If anyone comes,
you shoot them.
What are you talking about?
You shoot them.
What?
Victor.
Victor?
I said who is it?
It's me, Jess.
Jesus Christ, what
the fuck happened to you?
A long story.
Where's Victor?
He's dead.
He fell over the side.
How do we know
you didn't kill him?
You don't.
If you wanna live,
you'll follow me.
Downey!
Ignore it.
What's going on?
Is said ignore it.
Where are you? Call out.
No, I'm not just gonna ignore it.
What is going on?
Where
the fuck are you?
Call out! You're in danger.
You're in danger.
Who is that?
Not who you think?
So, what are we doing in here?
Sally!
Wait!
I'm sorry but I love my son.
Sally?
That wasn't me.
Hello? Hello?
Please, can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
She's killing everyone.
They're dead. They're all dead.
Please...
Sally?
What's your position? Over.
Sally.
Distressed caller, we hear you.
What are your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call?
We're not getting in anymore. Over.
Greg.
Greg, is that you?
Distressed caller, make another transmission.
What is your position?
Greg, can you hear me? Greg.
Shit.
Sally?
Oh, my God, what
happened to you?
Get away from me.
It wasn't me, Sally.
I didn't do this to you.
It wasn't me.
Where is Downey?
I don't know where he is.
You killed him.
What?
No, I didn't.
I didn't kill him.
What?
I swear.
You're crazy.
Why are you doing this?
Sally, I know it's hard
but you gotta trust me.
Gotta trust me, okay?
Listen, you gotta hold on.
I think it will return again.
The yacht, the Triangle,
I think it'll come back.
If it does, we'll escape,
me and you together.
We'll re-board it and escape.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
Sally, I'm not gonna hurt you.
If you hold on,
you can see Downey again.
Hey, come on. Over here.
Hey. Hey. Help.
It returns when they're dead.
It returns when
everyone's dead.
Do you think Heather
would've made it on board?
Honey.
There's a chance, isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah, there's a chance.
Stop this thing.
Stop this fucking thing.
Please.
I wanna go home.
He's dead. I mean, he was dead.
He's not dead now.
I was hiding and I saw
this version of myself,
and she had blood on her
face, and then I killed her.
I killed her on
the front of the ship.
Listen, I'm gonna
do you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell
anyone about this.
It's the truth.
You gotta listen to me.
No, I'm not listening
to another word you say.
You will die, and then
Greg and then Downey.
Don't be scared, Victor.
I can save you.
I know how to save you.
You should try and eat, babe.
Jess?
Jesus, what happened to you?
Where's Greg?
Greg told me to tell you we
should meet in the theater.
There's a theater?
Yes, it's just that way.
Where are you going?
I'll see you there.
Okay, she's really starting
to freak me out now.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just magically appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers.
In your world right
now maybe they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me
about my world.
Jess.
Jess, I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Okay.
Take it easy, man.
Just take it easy.
What did we do? We're
not part of this boat.
We just got here, okay? We've been walking around.
There's no one on it.
I can go right now. I will go.
Okay? Just... Just take it easy.
Take it easy.
Okay?
Jess?
Jess.
Jess, what are you doing?
Wha... what is this?
Why... what are you wearing?
I don't want you
to see my face.
Why?
Because this is not me.
I'm somewhere out there in the
yacht and you're with me.
And after I kill you,
we'll return.
Is that right?
You know, why-why don't you
just put down the gun first?
Okay? Come on.
You see, the boat comes
back when you're all dead.
I've done everything
exactly like before.
But when the boat comes back,
I'll be ready, I'll be waiting.
I'll be on the landing bay. I won't let
any of them board, even the other me.
I'll make them all stay
on the upturned yacht.
Okay.
Jess, we'll do
whatever you want.
Okay? Just, just
put down the gun.
Come on.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no!
Greg!
Oh, God! What happened?
It was Jess.
You fucking bitch! You shot him.
He said you shot him.
I wasn't even with Greg!
He's dead! He's dead!
My God, you're a
fucking skitso.
Downey!
Please.
Don't kill me.
I have a son.
Who are you?
Tell me!
They'll return.
Who are you?
You have to kill them.
It's the only way to get home.
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way
to save our son.
You have to kill them.
Kill them? Kill them?
Hurry up, Sweetheart.
We're gonna be late.
What's fun in buying you things
if you're gonna leave
them in the fucking garden!
I'm sick of telling
you this, Tommy.
I ain't buying you anymore toys if you
can't look after the ones you've got.
Now what?
Oh, I'll just
clean it up, shall I?
Yeah, I'm just cleaning
the fucking mess!
What's the matter with you, huh?
What's the matter with you?
Just one day off is all I ask.
Just one fucking day off!
I don't know why you can't paint
a picture like a normal kid.
You get this from your father.
He was an asshole, too.
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see anyone
ring my doorbell?
Tommy?
Sweetheart, come here.
Come here. Come here! It's okay.
Mommy's fine, you see?
Mommy's fine.
You're just having a bad dream.
That's all, baby.
It's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've
seen things that you haven't.
Things are gonna be
different now, Tommy.
Mommy won't lose
her temper anymore,
even when you do things wrong.
And she won't hurt you.
I know she won't hurt you.
You know how
I know that, Tommy?
Because that woman that did those
things to you is not Mommy.
This is Mommy. Mommy's nice.
Shit.
Tommy, stay in the car.
I'm gonna bury it, okay?
We have to go. We have
to get out of here.
Stop screaming, babe.
Please, Tommy, is just blood.
Stop screaming!
Tommy, look. See?
There, it's gone.
See? There. It's gone.
Are you all right?
Who are you?
Just a driver.
No point trying
to save the boy.
There's nothing anyone can do
that's gonna bring him back.
Can I give you a ride?
Yes.
Take me to the harbor.
Hey.
I'll leave the meter running.
You will come back, won't you?
Yes, I-I promise.
Jess.
Do you know me?
I feel like I do. Greg
talks about you enough.
Where is Greg?
Where do you think?
Come on, you're late.
You're the one
with the kid, right?
Yeah.
How come you didn't
bring him along?
He's at school.
You sure about that?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I don't think so.
Hey, what's the matter?
What happened?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
What's the matter?
I'm just tired.
Listen, we don't have to go
today if you don't want to.
No, I do. I-I wanna go.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Come, come here.
This is Sally and
her husband, Downey.
This is Heather, Sally's friend.
You remember Victor.
Let's go sailing.
Okay.