(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
JESS: Oh, you're just having a bad dream.
That's all, baby.
That's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've
seen things that you haven't.
You know what I do
when I have a bad dream?
I close my eyes and
I think of something nice.
Like being here with you.
Hurry up, sweetheart.
We're gonna be late.
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(WHISPERING)
Shit.
(LAWNMOWER RUNNING)
Jack?
Did you see someone
ring my doorbell?
JACK: No.
JESS: Okay, thanks.
I cleaned everything away,
sweetheart.
Everything is exactly
the way it was before.
Look, look, the floor is shiny.
They're clean and shiny. Look. Look. You see?
(CRYING)
Okay, all right.
Just close your eyes.
DOWNEY: Well, hello, sailor.
SALLY: Hi!
Permission to come aboard?
Honey, hold this.
So sorry we couldn't make it yesterday.
Somebody was working late again.
How're you doing, Sal?
I'm good.
How are you?
I'm all right.
Look at you.
What? Do you like it?
You look great.
Really? Oh, it's nothing.
I just kinda threw it on.
Bullshit, she's had outfits
laid out for a week.
You're such a liar.
You know my husband a bit.
I don't listen to a word what he says.
You know that.
Oh, I brought my really good friend,
Heather. She's so nice.
So, promise me you'll be attentive.
How're you doing, man?
I asked her to not bring anyone.
You don't like her? Believe me,
she's the best looking of Sally's friends.
Which gladly isn't saying much.
I asked you not to.
What? You're living on a boat with an 18-year
old boy and you're asking me not to bring girls.
Greg, this is Heather.
She's a very good friend of mine,
and I just thought you guys should meet.
Hi.
- Hi.
Can you just excuse me
for a moment?
Jess. You okay?
I don't think so.
Hey. What happened?
Hey. What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing
to apologize for.
What is it?
Are you okay?
I'm just tired.
Well, listen, we don't have to
go today if you don't want to.
No, we do.
I-I wanna go.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay, come on.
Come we get together.
- This is Sally and her husband, Downey. And...
- (BOTH) Hi. Hi.
...this is Heather, Sally's friend.
You remember Victor.
So let's go sailing!
Okay.
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
HEATHER: Hey.
You okay?
Is Greg okay?
He's fine.
He's upstairs.
You've been asleep
for a couple of hours.
I had this terrible dream.
What about?
I don't remember.
I wouldn't worry.
Apparently bad dreams cure
you of real life stress.
As indeed does champagne.
You want some?
Yeah.
Downey, wanna give me
a hand, please?
Well, actually, Victor, I'm a guest of the
Captain's, but yes, I will help you.
Victor, what was that
back there at the harbor?
What?
When I asked Jess if she was
all right and you said no.
Well, you told me she was bringing
the little boy along.
Yeah.
So, when I was walking with her in
the harbor I asked where he was.
She couldn't remember.
She stared into space
for like 20 seconds
and then she said
he's at school.
So?
Well, it's Saturday.
Ain't no school today.
Her son goes to a special needs
school and it's open every day.
Be nice to her.
All right.
So, do you boys sunbathe together?
Sometimes.
The champagne is not great
but it is cold. Want some?
No thanks.
Okay, more for me.
Hey, how are you feeling?
I'm sorry, I didn't
realize how tired I was.
You apologize one more time,
and I'm gonna throw you overboard.
Here.
You all right?
Yeah.
(SEAGULL SQUAWKING)
He thinks we're a fishing boat.
He's gonna go hungry.
You want to steer?
Nah.
Go on.
Which way do I aim?
You're gonna aim that way.
It's easy, right?
HEATHER: So, she's a waitress
at some diner.
At least there they talk.
They became friends.
Oh, and she has an autistic son.
So they're just friends.
Sally!
What do you want me to say?
I'm sorry she has a retarded son?
- Yeah!
- Well, I'm sorry.
You know, that's not Greg's problem,
that's hers.
What is it, is it the shorts?
No! Heather, Greg's been my
friend for a really long time.
I can't just sit back and
watch him get shaken down.
She isn't doing that.
Well, I hope not because
Greg is far too trusting.
I'm kinda liking the boy.
Uh, no, you're not. Can you please
go up there and talk to Greg?
I just... I really think the two of you
will be perfect for each other.
And I really don't like
seeing him with her.
Jess, are you ready?
Yeah, let her go.
Yeah.
Woo!
JESS: So, how do you know everyone?
Victor, he's staying
with me for good.
He got in some trouble at home.
He had to get away.
I found him sleeping behind
the store at the harbor.
You know, we got talking,
and now he lives here.
Just like that
you let him move in?
Well, I got three rooms.
I can't sleep in them all.
And Downey, I've known
him since I was a kid.
Sally, his wife,
I know her from high school.
I dated her for like four
days in the eighth grade,
so technically she's my ex.
They seem really nice.
Yeah. Except for the fact that
every year they feel obliged
to bring me an eligible girl.
Maybe they think you're lonely.
Do I give off lonely to you?
Sometimes.
When I come to see you at the diner,
I'm not lonely, I'm hungry.
Obviously yesterday was different.
What happened yesterday?
Yesterday I was not hungry.
I came in with the sole purpose
of inviting you sailing.
You did?
I did.
Hey, turn at port side.
We're losing wind.
Yeah, let me check it for just a sec.
So, things are okay with Tommy?
The same.
Every day is the same.
Tommy likes the things
to be a certain way. Yeah.
If I do one thing differently,
I lose him.
What's the matter?
I've never seen you like this before.
I don't know. I just, uh, I just
feel guilty when I'm not with Tommy.
That's because you're a good mother.
But you can't be everywhere
all of the times.
Hey, guys. Oh!
(LAUGHS)
How is it going?
We're good.
I was just wondering if I could
steal Jess away from you.
Sally's dying to talk to her.
We're kind of in the middle
of something right now.
No, no, no, it's okay.
I-I should circulate.
Hey, just for the record,
I'm not interested.
Yo, what the fuck?
Wind's dropped down on us.
It's not dropped, it's gone.
VICTOR: This is crazy.
You ever seen this before?
Yeah, yeah.
Just not quite so sudden.
Are we okay to get home?
There is no wind.
Yeah, yeah. We got an engine.
It's not a problem.
It's just, it's weird.
Greg?
Is that normal?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
DOWNEY: Okay, I'm fucking freaked now,
what the fuck.
Triangle to coast guard. Over.
(RADIO STATICS)
(STATICS)
Coast guard, go ahead. Over.
We've just gone from seven knots to absolute zero.
You've got anything unusual? Over?
Nothing showing up. Over.
It's darkening up pretty quick out here.
Looks like an electrical storm. Over.
DISTRESSED CALLER: Help me. Please.
Can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
Killing everyone. They're dead.
They're all dead.
GREG: (OVER RADIO) We hear you.
What's your position? Over.
(STATICS)
Distressed caller, we hear you.
What are your coordinates? Over.
(STATICS)
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call?
We're not getting it anymore. Over.
Distressed caller, make another transmission.
What is your position?
HEATHER: Greg?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Get below deck now.
Get the life jackets.
Cut it. Cut the sail.
Vic, get the main sail down.
Get it down.
(SCREAMING)
Vic!
No!
(SCREAMS)
Get back.
JESS: (SCREAMING)
Jess, take my hand.
Grab on.
Heather!
Vic!
Jess.
Are you okay?
Are you all right.
DOWNEY: (COUGHING)
Downey?
Are you guys okay?
Have you seen Heather?
She got lost through the window.
- No. Come on, come on.
- Oh, my God!
Heather!
Greg! Help me!
GREG: Sally. Sally, come on.
SALLY: Help me!
SALLY: Did you see her?
GREG: Just give me your hand.
SALLY: Heather!
GREG: Sally, come on.
Are you guys okay?
Yeah.
Are you all right?
Tommy's at school, yeah?
He'll be looked after until we get back.
He'll be all right.
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Thank God. Yo!
Help us!
ALL: Help us. Help. Please. Hello!
Help us. Hey, over here. Please.
Oh, God.
- Hey! Hey!
- Over here!
ALL: Wait. Please.
Hey, come on, over here! Hello!
- There, there. Over there. I can see someone.
- Yeah.
VICTOR: Yo, we need
some help down here.
SALLY: Help us, please!
VICTOR: Hey! Hey!
Hello.
Look, we need some help down here.
Yeah, he's seen us.
He's seen us.
GREG: Oh, thank God.
Jump, jump, jump.
Okay. Jess, come on, come on.
Jess. Come on.
Come on, come on,
take my hand. Okay.
Okay. You made it. You okay?
DOWNEY: You okay? Yeah?
SALLY: (CRYING)
- Okay.
- What do we do now?
Hey. How it's going? Yeah.
GREG: See? I told you. Are you okay.
SALLY: I know.
VICTOR: Hello?
Hello?
Hello!
Do we wait?
GREG: No, let's go to the bridge.
DOWNEY: Yeah.
We'll get the captain to put
a call out to the coast guard.
- All right. We'll get a search for Heather.
- SALLY: (SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
Come on.
Do you think Heather
would've made it on board?
DOWNEY: Honey.
There's a chance, isn't there?
DOWNEY: Yeah. Yeah, there's a chance.
Hello?
Hello!
SALLY: Somebody please help us?
Hello?
VICTOR: Where the fuck is everybody?
DOWNEY: Do you even know where we're going?
GREG: Un-huh.
GREG: Well, we're just, just
walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
VICTOR: Come check this out.
This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
Jess.
- Come on. Come on.
- Yeah.
1932. It is the same. See...
Here's where we boarded.
Oh, yeah.
Ae-o-lus.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek God of the
winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the Gods to the
task of pushing a rock up a mountain
only to have it
roll back down again.
That's a pretty shitty punishment.
What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a
promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied it but I can't remember.
Can we just keep on moving, please?
(CLANKING)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
Hello?
Whoever it was might wanna
come back for these.
Let me see?
These are mine.
These are my keys.
What are you talking about?
They're mine.
Bullshit.
This is, this is my house key.
This is my, my car key.
This is my son. See?
Wait. So you had them
with you on the yacht?
Yes.
It's gotta be Heather.
Oh, come on.
Well, how else did they get here?
You're saying it was Heather dropping her keys
but not bothering to stop and say,
"Hey people, guess what, I didn't drown."
Well, why not?
GREG: Come on.
SALLY: Heather?
Looks like you get your welcome party,
just not the welcome.
Heather!
Yo, Greg, what time you got?
Eleven thirty.
Heather.
Heather!
Where is everyone?
Sally! Please. Please.
I don't-I don't know where everyone is
but-but the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think
that it is but it's not,
so let's just go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we'll go home.
JESS: I saw someone.
Fuck.
Wait.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(LOUD THUD)
Hello?
Well, did you see who it was?
Was it Heather?
I didn't see.
I'm sorry.
DOWNEY: Where're you going?
Why don't you
just help me out here?
What?
Just wait for Vic.
It's okay. It's fine.
Why can't we go with him?
Look, let's just do as Greg says
and wait here for Victor, okay?
Fine.
I think Victor's in danger.
I'm not worried about Victor.
I'm sorry I'm acting weird, Greg.
It's just I'm having déjà vu
every time I turn a corner.
No, no, no. No.
I know this place.
No, you don't know this place.
You're just in shock.
That's funny.
What is it? What is it?
Is it Tommy?
Is it guilt? Is that what it is?
Do you feel guilty?
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
Hello?
GO TO THEATER
Hello.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLANKING)
Hello.
- So, we're on the third floor.
- Greg.
The bridge is exactly two floors above us.
- Greg, that was blood.
- That's exactly where we wanna go.
Are you just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
You know, they see us, they get bored.
They're just letting off some steam.
What? They rescue us from the sea
and then they just hide for fun?
Yeah.
Well, what's your theory?
I don't know, but I'm not,
but I'm not in shock.
I'll be in the ball room.
I'm getting off this ship.
Jess, fuck! Don't you-Don't you see
that this is all just in your mind?
Jess! Ships don't just magically
appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean,
in your world right now maybe they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
Jess.
Jess, I'm sorry.
Shit.
SALLY: Is that blood?
DOWNEY: Babe, come on, we're supposed
to meet them in the theater.
Heather!
Oh, my God. Shit.
Sally. Sal, come on.
Let's just go to the theater.
Downey, I can't see anymore blood.
I don't think she's in here.
Got to be honest with you honey,
I don't think she's even on the ship.
Okay. So whose blood was that?
JESS: Hello?
Downey? Sally?
(DOOR OPENS)
(THUDS)
Victor. What happened?
(GASPS)
Oh, my God.
(GUNSHOTS)
DOWNEY: Stay with me, Greg.
Stay with me, man.
SALLY: (CRYING)
No. No!
You-You fucking bitch!
You shot him!
What?
He said you shot him.
- What? I didn't! What're you talking about?
- Don't you lie, liar.
You fucking liar!
I wasn't even with Greg!
Christ! He's dead! He's dead! Look!
God, you're a bitch!
JESS: (SOBBING)
Get your hands off him!
I didn't do it!
I was with Victor.
Someone attacked him.
Someone?
You think I did it?
Why did you tell us
to come to the theater?
I didn't. I... Sally, I didn't.
I didn't.
My God, you're a fucking skitzo.
SALLY: (SCREAMING)
No! Sally, no.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Downey! Downey!
- DOWNEY: (GROANING)
- SALLY: Oh, God!
- SALLY: (SCREAMING) Downey!
- DOWNEY: Jesus Christ!
Sally!
No! Oh!
(CRYING)
Oh, God. Downey!
(SCREAMS)
Let it go. Let it go.
(SHOUTING)
No!
(GUNSHOTS)
(LOUD CLANKS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
Don't shoot. Please.
Please, don't shoot. Please.
I have a son. I have a son.
(GUNSHOTS)
Shit.
Who are you? Tell me!
Who are you?
(MUFFLED VOICE)
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way to get home.
What?
You have to kill them.
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them!
(DISTANT SQUAWKING)
(SQUAWKING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STARTS)
(VOICES SHOUTING)
ALL: Hey! Hey! Help us. Help. Somebody help please.
Hello! Please. Help us. Hey, over here. Come on.
ALL: Hey! Help us. Wait. Please.
Over here! Hey, come on. Hey! Hey!
- SALLY: Help us, please!
- GREG: Hello!
Help!
- Hey! Hey!
- Over here!
- Help us!
- Hey!
Please!
There, there. Over there.
I can see somebody.
SALLY: Please!
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(MUSIC STARTS)
VICTOR: Hello?
Looks like they decided
to scratch the welcome.
GREG: No, let's go to the bridge.
DOWNEY: Yeah.
We'll get the captain to put
a call out to the coast guard.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello!
Hello?
VICTOR: Where the fuck is everybody?
DOWNEY: Do you even know
where we're going?
Well, we're just, just
walking for the sake of it.
You all right?
I feel like I know this place.
I recognize this corridor.
Liners, they look pretty similar.
No, that's not it.
Jess, come on.
VICTOR: This is the same ship.
This thing's old.
DOWNEY: Yeah. 1932.
It is the same. See...
Here's where we boarded.
Oh, yeah.
Ae-o-lus.
Aeolus.
Aeolus was the Greek God of the
winds and the father of Sisyphus,
the man condemned by the Gods to the
task of pushing a rock up a mountain
only to have it
roll back down again.
That's a pretty shitty punishment.
What did he do?
He cheated Death. No, he made a
promise to Death that he didn't keep.
I studied it but I can't remember.
Can we just keep on moving, please?
Hello?
SALLY: Heather?
VICTOR: Hello!
Heather!
GREG: Sally. Please. Please.
I don't-I don't know where everyone is...
...but-but the ship's not deserted.
I mean, maybe some of us think
that it is but it's not,
so let's just go to the bridge.
We'll find the skipper
and then we'll go home.
JESS: I saw someone.
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
Hello?
Hello.
Shit.
How did you get here so fast?
Victor, you got, you gotta listen to me.
We don't have much time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's going on?
Where's Greg?
He's dead.
What?
No, no, no. I-I mean, he was dead.
He's-he's not dead now.
What are you saying?
Downstairs right now
is a copy of myself.
Me, walking and talking with Greg.
- Right. What?
- Shit.
There.
There's birds.
No, that was Downey's body.
I just left Downey back there.
How did you get here so fast?
That's what I've been
trying to tell you.
(SQUAWKING)
No. Downey was there.
It was-It was Downey's body.
There are bodies
all over this ship.
Your body is on the floor at the
restaurant with a hole in your head.
Listen, I'm gonna do you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell anyone about this.
It's the truth. Victor,
we gotta get off this ship right now.
You're saying there's two of you now.
Yes.
And I'm dead in the restaurant.
You were killed.
Okay. So, I'm dead. Downey's in the water.
He's dead, too.
Is Sally okay?
See where I'm going with this, right?
I mean, if we are dead and
there's two of you,
how are we all gonna
get off this ship?
We should never have
boarded this ship.
I knew something was wrong.
I should've-I should've forced you to stay
on the yacht and then you'd all be alive.
I've gotta tell you
I feel pretty alive right now.
- Soon you're gonna be dead, Victor.
- Hey, easy on the grabbing.
Everything that happened to you,
happened to you before.
I can't-I can't even believe
I'm talking this shit.
Victor, you're just gonna die.
You will die and then-and then,
Downey and Sally and then Greg.
(GROANS)
I didn't do this.
GREG: All right, we're on the third level.
The bridge is exactly two floors above us.
Greg, that was blood.
Are you just gonna ignore it?
I know guys that work
on ships like this.
You know, they see us, they get bored.
They're just letting off some steam.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just magically
appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers. I mean,
in your world right now maybe they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
(SOBBING)
JESS: Who are you?
Who are you?
If they board, kill them all
(ECHOING SHOUTS)
Who are you?
Listen, listen to me.
- Please, you have to listen.
- (ECHOING SHOUTS) Who are you?
You have to kill them all.
- If they board, kill them.
- (ECHOING SHOUTS) Who are you?
Jess. Jess, you gotta kill them.
Please, you have to listen.
Don't-Don't let them board.
No, no. No. Please, please.
Stop, stop them.
If they board, kill them.
Jess. Jess, you gotta kill them.
No, no. No. Please, please, stop.
If they board, kill them.
Please, please stop. If they board...
Jess, Jess, Jess.
Fuck you!
(SOBBING)
Shit.
Tommy.
SALLY: Is that blood?
Babe, come on. We're supposed
to meet them at the theater.
Victor.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
You know I didn't mean
to hurt you, right?
Now, I'm gonna try and get
us off this ship, okay?
JESS: Sally.
Sally?
Victor?
What happened?
You're not me.
(WHISPERING)
You see?
I'm not crazy.
Victor.
This didn't happen before.
Don't you see?
You tried to strangle me, remember?
Now, you gotta be strong.
I'm gonna get the others. Okay.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Oh, God.
SALLY: (CRYING)
Downey, do something.
Stay with me, man.
Do something.
I don't know what to do.
- Is he dead? Is he dead?
- I don't know what to do.
Greg. Oh, Greg.
You fucking...
Listen, I'm not gonna hurt you.
We-We don't have much time.
Don't you point that thing at my...
- Move!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- Go, go, go, go.
- Go!
(GUNSHOTS)
I hit her.
I think I hit her.
What's going on?
Who was that?
It's starting all over again.
That's what's going on.
- Oh, no.
- Let's go.
- No, we can't leave without Greg. Downey, please.
- We'll come back for Greg. I promise.
Let's go, come on!
We can change the pattern.
Don't you see?
We change the pattern, we're not trapped.
Then we get off this thing.
Oh, Jesus, she's fucking mad.
You think?
You have to listen to me.
No, I don't have to listen to you.
Yes, you think it was me
who fired that shot at you?
- I don't know.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait.
Could we just take a
breath here for a second?
Okay, Jess,
I am prepared to listen to you
and even prepared to believe you,
but you gotta start making some sense.
I'm making perfect sense. I'm gonna get
Victor, then we get off this ship.
Wait here.
And don't trust anyone.
If anyone comes, you shoot them.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You shoot them.
What?
(WHISPERING)
Victor.
Victor?
(GUNSHOTS)
I said who is it?
It's me, Jess.
Jesus Christ,
what the fuck happened to you?
A long story.
Where's Victor?
He's dead.
He fell over the side.
How do we know you didn't kill him?
You don't.
If you wanna live,
you'll follow me.
Downey!
Ignore it.
What's going on?
I said ignore it.
Where are you?
Call out.
No, I'm not just gonna ignore it.
What is going on?
JESS: (WHISPERING)
Where the fuck are you?
Call out! You're in danger.
(ECHOING) You're in danger.
Who is that?
Not who you think?
So, what are we doing in here?
SALLY: (SCREAMING)
JESS: Sally!
Wait!
I'm sorry but I love my son.
(GROANS)
Sally?
That wasn't me.
SALLY: (CRYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Sally?
Come on.
SALLY: Hello? Hello?
Please, can you hear me?
Help me. Please, help me.
She's killing everyone.
They're dead. They're all dead.
Please...
- ...help.
- Sally?
GREG: (OVER RADIO)  We hear you.
What's your position? Over.
Sally.
Distressed caller, we hear you.
What are your coordinates? Over.
Coast guard, did you hear a distress call?
We're not getting in anymore. Over.
Greg.
Greg, is that you?
(STATICS)
Distressed caller, make another transmission.
What is your position?
Greg, can you hear me? Greg.
(STATICS)
Shit.
Sally?
SALLY: (GROANING)
(CRYING)
Oh, my God,
what happened to you?
Get-Get away from me.
It wasn't me, Sally.
I didn't do this to you.
(WHISPERING)
It wasn't me. Where is Downey?
I don't know where he is.
You killed him.
What?
No, I didn't.
I didn't kill him.
What?
I swear.
You're crazy. (CRYING)
Why are you doing this?
Listen, Sally, I know it's hard
but you gotta trust me.
Gotta trust me, okay?
Listen, you gotta hold on.
I think it will return again.
The yacht, the Triangle,
I think it'll come back.
If it does, we'll escape on it,
me and you together.
We'll re-board it and escape.
Please.
Don't hurt me.
Sally, I'm not gonna hurt you.
If you hold on,
you can see Downey again.
(SQUAWKING)
(VOICES SHOUTING)
ALL: Hey, over here. Hey! Hey! Help us.
ALL: Hey, help us. Over here.
Hey, come on.
ALL: Hey. Hey. Help. Help us.
JESS: It returns when they're dead.
It returns when everyone's dead.
SALLY: Do you think Heather
would've made it on board?
DOWNEY: Honey.
SALLY: There's a chance, isn't there?
DOWNEY: Yeah. Yeah, there's a chance.
JESS: Stop this thing.
Stop this fucking thing.
Please.
I wanna go home.
JESS: He's dead.
VICTOR: What?
No, no, no. I-I mean, he was dead.
He's-he's not dead now.
I was hiding in the furnace
and I saw this version of myself,
and she-she had blood on one side
of her face, and then I-I killed her.
I killed her on
the front of the ship.
Listen, I'm gonna do you a favor, okay?
I'm not gonna tell anyone about this.
It's the truth.
You gotta listen to me.
No, I'm not listening
to another word you say.
It means you're gonna be die.
You'll die, and then
Greg and then Downey.
Oh God.
- VICTOR: (GROANS)
- (RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(GROANS)
Don't be scared, Victor.
I can save you.
I know how to save you.
You should try and eat, babe.
Jess?
Jesus, what happened to you?
Where's Greg?
Greg told me to tell you we
should meet in the theater.
There's a theater?
Yes, it's just that way.
Where are you going?
I'll see you there.
Okay, she's really starting
to freak me out now.
Don't you see that this
is all just in your mind?
Ships don't just magically appear out of nowhere.
They have skippers.
I mean, in your world right now
maybe they don't.
My world is waiting outside school
for his mother to pick him up.
Don't talk to me about my world.
Jess.
Jess, I'm sorry.
Whoa. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Just...
Okay.
Take it easy, man.
Just take it easy.
What did we do?
We're not part of this boat.
We just-We just got here, okay?
We-We've been walking around.
There's-There's no one on it.
I mean, you know, I-I can go right now.
I will go.
Okay? Just... Just take it easy.
Take it easy.
Okay?
Jess?
Jess.
Jess, what are you doing?
What-What is this?
Why-Why... What-What are you wearing?
I don't want you to see my face.
Why?
Because this is not me.
I'm somewhere out there in the
upturned yacht and you're with me.
And after I kill you,
we'll return.
Is that right?
You know, why-why don't you
just put down the gun first?
Okay? Come on.
You see, the boat comes back
when you're all dead.
I've done everything
exactly like... before.
But when the boat comes back,
I'll be ready, I'll be waiting.
I'll be on the landing bay. I won't let
any of them board, even the other me.
I-I'll make them all stay
on the upturned yacht.
Okay.
Jess, we'll do whatever you want.
Okay?
Just, just put down the gun.
Come on.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, no!
(GUNSHOTS)
SALLY: (SHOUTING)
Greg!
- Oh, God! What happened?
- DOWNEY: Greg!
- GREG: It was Jess.
- Help!
- You-You fucking bitch! You shot him.
- JESS: What?
He said you shot him.
I wasn't even with Greg!
Christ! He's dead! He's dead!
- My God, you're a fucking skitzo.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- SALLY: (SCREAMING)
Downey! Downey!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (SCREAMING)
Oh, honey!
(CRYING)
(GUNSHOTS)
JESS: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Please.
Don't kill me.
I have a son.
(GUNSHOTS)
Who are you?
Tell me!
They'll return.
Who are you?
You have to kill them.
It's the only way to get home.
What the fuck are you saying?
It's the only way
to save our son.
You have to kill them.
Kill them? Kill them?
JESS: Hurry up, sweetheart.
We're gonna be late.
What's fun in buying you things
if you're just gonna leave
them in the fucking garden!
I'm sick of telling you this, Tommy.
I ain't buying you anymore toys if you
can't look after the ones you've got.
Now what?
Oh, I'll just clean it up,
shall I? (SLAPPING)
Yeah, I'm just cleaning
the fucking mess!
I mean, what's the matter with you, huh?
What's the matter with you?
Just one day off is all I ask.
Just one fucking day off!
I don't know why you can't paint
a picture like a normal kid.
You know, you get this from your father.
He was an asshole, too.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(WHISPERING)
Shit.
Jack?
Did you see anyone
ring my doorbell?
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES, LOCKS)
JESS: Tommy?
(PANTING)
Sweetheart, come here.
Come here. It's... Come here!
It's all right. It's okay. It's okay.
- TOMMY: (CRYING)
- JESS: It's okay.
Mommy's fine, you see?
Mommy's fine.
Oh, you're just having a bad dream.
That's all, baby.
That's all it was.
Bad dreams make you think you've
seen things that you haven't.
(CLOSET OPENS)
(CLOSET CLOSES)
(CAR TRUNK CLOSES)
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Things are gonna be
different now, Tommy.
Mommy won't lose
her temper anymore,
even when you do things wrong.
And she won't hurt you.
I know she won't hurt you.
You know how I know that, Tommy?
Because that woman that did those
things to you is not Mommy.
- This is Mommy. Mommy's nice.
- (THUD)
Shit.
TOMMY: (CRYING)
Tommy, stay in the car.
Mommy will bury it, okay?
(BAND PLAYING)
TOMMY: (PANTING)
We have to go.
We have to get out of here.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Stop screaming, babe.
TOMMY: (CRYING) Mom!
Please, Tommy, it's just blood.
Stop screaming!
Tommy, look. See?
There, it's gone.
- See? There. It's gone.
- Mommy! No!
(TRUCK HORN BLARES)
- (METAL SCREECHES)
- (GLASS BREAKS)
(LOUD THUD)
Are you all right?
Who are you?
Just a driver.
No point trying to save the boy.
There's nothing anyone can do
that's gonna bring him back.
Can I give you a ride?
Yes.
Take me to the harbor.
Hey.
I'll leave the meter running.
You will come back, won't you?
Yes, I-I promise.
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
VICTOR: Jess.
Do you know me?
I feel like I do.
Greg talks about you enough.
Where is Greg?
Where do you think?
Come on, you're late.
You're the one
with the kid, right?
Yeah.
Then how come you didn't
bring him along?
He's at school.
You sure about that?
Yes.
GREG: Are you okay?
VICTOR: I don't think so.
Hey, what's the matter?
What happened?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
What's the matter?
I'm just tired.
Well, listen, we don't have to
go today if you don't want to.
No, I do.
I-I wanna go.
Are you sure?
(WHISPERING)
Yeah.
Yeah? Okay, come on.
This is Sally and her husband,
Downey. And...
SALLY: Hi.
This is Heather, Sally's friend.
- You remember Victor.
- HEATHER: Hi.
So let's go sailing.
Okay.
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
Subtitles by MoSub